irely.in 2016-03-23

# Privacy Policy Online in Bangalore and Hyderabad - iRely.in

Privacy Policy  
This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.  
This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and Terms of Use for access or usage of www.irely.in website.  
The domain name www.irely.in (hereinafter referred to as "Website" or “Site”) is owned by Rajtek Home Solutions, a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 with its registered office at #109, 3rd A Cross, PR Layout, Munnekolala Ext, Marathahalli, Bangalore, Karnataka, India-560037 (hereinafter referred to as “iRely.in”).  
For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, wherever the context so requires "You" or “User” shall mean any natural or legal person who accesses the Website or has agreed to become a buyer on the Website by providing Registration Data while registering on the Website as Registered User using the computer systems. iRely.in allows the User to surf the Website without registering on the Website. Making a purchase on the Website requires the User to be registered with the Website. The term “We”, “Us”, “Our” shall mean Rajtek Home Solutions or iRely.in.  
iRely.in respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which IRely.in collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from User of the Website. This privacy policy applies to the Website and all products and services offered by IRely.in through the Website. We suggest you to read the privacy policy carefully. By using the site and accessing the services provided by the site, You, as a User, agree to the collection and use of your data by iRely.in in the manner provided in this privacy policy.  
Collection of Information  
 Personal Identification Information  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, alternate phone number, alternate email address, and demographic profile such as age, gender, occupation, marital status, name and age of children etc.   
Non-personal identification information  
 We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information. We also collect information about the pages on our site the User visit/access, the links User click on our site, the number of times User access the page, key words User uses to search in our site.  
Web browser cookies  
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

User’s role in Collection of Information  
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply Personal Identification Information, except that it may prevent them from placing an order from the website. It is purely at the will of the User to opt for marketing, promotional and/or newsletter mails. However, sending the mails that are required for customer communication in the process of fulfilling the services provided by the Site is under sole discretion of IRely.in.  
Updating and Deleting the User Information  
User can request for and update the existing information at any point in time through the website. User can request for deletion of the collected Personal Information through the Site or by contacting us. This request deletes the account information from the database and releases the User from being a registered user. However, the Site still carries a trace of the User details in its archives and other records pertaining to the period in which User was registered.  
Usage of Collected Information

IRely.in collects and uses User’s personal information for the following purposes:  
To improve customer service:

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users, individually and/or as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

To personalize user experience:   
User information helps us to more effectively respond to his/her customer service requests and support needs.

To improve our Site:

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

To process transactions:  
We may use the information that the User provides when requesting a service only to serve the request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature:

We my use the information to send Users the information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. We may also use the information to administer promotional offers through our business associates and partners, to get in touch with Users when necessary, to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy, to contact User as a survey respondent, to notify User if he/she wins any contest and to send User any promotional material from our contest sponsors or advertisers.

To send periodic emails:  
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.  
Sharing the Information  
We will not use User’s financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. We do not rent, sell or share their personal information to any third party. We will not disclose any of the user’s personally identifiable information to third parties unless we have User’s permission to provide products or services that the user has requested. We may share the information with our business associates and partners for promotional offers.  
We may share the information to any Government Agency to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of iRely.in’s terms of use or to defend against legal claims. We may also disclose information to the Government agencies or legal authorities or any other law enforcement agencies while handling requests/order from them.  
 Protection of User information  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Internally, the Personal Information is accessed by the authorized personnel on a need to know basis for the fulfilment of the transaction requested by the user. In spite of these measures to protect user information, due to several reasons, the transmissions made over the Internet are not entirely safe. We are not responsible for any kind of disclosures caused by the errors in transmission or any unauthorized actions of third parties.   
Third party websites  
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which we do not own, manage or control.  
Advertising  
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks too, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. We are not responsible for the Information collected by the advertisers.  
Google Adsense  
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google\'s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy athttp://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. You can also opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.  
Changes to this privacy policy   
We reserve the right, at Our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy, at any time without any prior written notice to You. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. User should acknowledge and agree that it is his/her responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.  
Acceptance of these terms  
By using this Site, you as a User signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Rajtek Home Solutions  
www.irely.in

Rajtek Home Solutions, #109, 3rd A Cross, PR Layout, Munnekolala Ext, Marathahalli, Bangalore, Karnataka, India-560037   
+919886718121  
customercare@irely.in
